<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>WSBSD RSS News Channel 1</title>
    <link>https://coolis1362.github.io/wsbsd.org/news.html</link>
    <description>Latest releases and updates from WSBSD</description>
    <item>
      <title>WSBSD 1.0.0.4-5 Is Delayed</title>
      <link>https://coolis1362.github.io/wsbsd.org/annoucements/1.0.0.4-5.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 May 2025 9:20:51 EDT</pubDate>
      <description>We regret to inform you that the release of WSBSD 1.0.0.4-5 has been delayed. We have a busy summer ahead of us, the estimated release date is now August 31st 2025. Sorry the delay will be long. We Are now pausing the WSBSD Project and 1.0.0.4-5 brainstorming.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WSBSD RSS News Channel 1 Launched</title>
      <link>https://coolis1362.github.io/wsbsd.org/wsbsdrssnewschannels/channel1/feed.xml</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 May 2025 9:43 EDT</pubDate>
      <description>We are pleased to announce the launch of WSBSD RSS News Channel 1. This channel will provide updates on the latest releases and developments in the WSBSD project. The Other email that's Older then this email is a test of WSBSD RSS News Channel 1. 😊😀 The Link you see is the xml code of WSBSD RSS News Channel 1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
     <title>WSBSD RSS News Channel 1 Daily Broadcast Cycle</title>
     <link>https://coolis1362.github.io/wsbsd.org/wsbsdrssnewschannels/channel1/feed.xml</link>
     <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 09:43:00 EDT</pubDate>
     <description>
     WSBSD RSS News Channel 1 is now active. This feed follows a structured broadcast cycle designed to simulate a digital comms system.

     News updates will be shared throughout the day. A system status line will appear at the bottom of each RSS email, reflecting the channel's current state.

     ——
     <strong>Channel Status Codes:</strong>

     • <strong>SFTD</strong> (Starting For The Day) — Uplink initialized. Broadcasting begins.  
     • <strong>OPERATIONAL</strong> — Actively transmitting news or monitoring system state.  
     • <strong>UPDATING</strong> — Feed is being modified. New &lt;item&gt; queued or deployed.  
     • <strong>IDLE</strong> — No current updates, channel on standby.  
     • <strong>DFTD</strong> (Done For The Day) — Broadcasting paused. Channel offline until next cycle.
  </description>
</item>
  </channel>
</rss>
