<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>WSBSD RSS News Channel 1</title>
    <link>https://coolis1362.github.io/wsbsd.org/news.html</link>
    <description>
     WSBSD RSS News Channel 1 delivers structured daily transmissions from the WSBSD project. This channel shares version updates, delays, announcements, and system status logs—formatted like mission briefings.

     Each broadcast includes a status signature (e.g. SFTD, OPERATIONAL, DFTD) to simulate the WSBSD system's state throughout the cycle. Channel 1 is the flagship node in the WSBSD RSS network.
    </description>

    <item>
      <title>WSBSD 1.0.0.4-5 Is Delayed</title>
      <link>https://coolis1362.github.io/wsbsd.org/annoucements/1.0.0.4-5.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 May 2025 9:20:51 -0400</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[ We regret to inform you that the release of WSBSD 1.0.0.4-5 has been delayed. We have a busy summer ahead of us, the estimated release date is now August 31st 2025. Sorry the delay will be long. We Are now pausing the WSBSD Project and 1.0.0.4-5 brainstorming.]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WSBSD RSS News Channel 1 Launched</title>
      <link>https://coolis1362.github.io/wsbsd.org/wsbsdrssnewschannels/channel1/feed.xml</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 May 2025 9:43 -0400</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[ We are pleased to announce the launch of WSBSD RSS News Channel 1. This channel will provide updates on the latest releases and developments in the WSBSD project. The Other email that's Older then this email is a test of WSBSD RSS News Channel 1. 😊😀 The Link you see is the xml code of WSBSD RSS News Channel 1. STATUS: WSBSD/IDLE]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
     <title>WSBSD RSS News Channel 1 Daily Broadcast Cycle</title>
     <link>https://coolis1362.github.io/wsbsd.org/wsbsdrssnewschannels/channel1/feed.xml</link>
     <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 09:43 -0400</pubDate>
     <description><![CDATA[
       WSBSD RSS News Channel 1 is now active. This feed follows a structured broadcast cycle...

       ——
       Channel Status Codes:

       • SFTD (Starting For The Day) — Uplink initialized. Broadcasting begins.  
       • OPERATIONAL — Actively transmitting news or monitoring system state.  
       • UPDATING — Feed is being modified. New <item> queued or deployed.  
       • IDLE — No current updates, channel on standby.  
       • DFTD (Done For The Day) — Broadcasting paused. Channel offline until next cycle.
     ]]></description>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WSBSD 1.0.0.4-5 Delay Stops</title>
      <link>https://coolis1362.github.io/wsbsd.org/annoucements/1.0.0.4-5.html</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2025 -0400</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[ We are pleased to announce that the delay for WSBSD 1.0.0.4-5 has been lifted. Development is back on track, and we are working hard to meet the new release date. Looks Like Our Busy summer is shorter then expected!]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
